europacbank.com 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy | Euro Pacific Bank

Euro Pacific Intl. Bank Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (herein referred to as “Euro Pacific Bank”, “The Bank”) constantly develop and implement security enhancements to ensure the confidentiality of your personal, non-public information while accessing your online account. The bank reserves the right, at its sole discretion to change, modify, add or remove sections of this privacy policy; by using this website and our online banking platform you provide consent and confirm that you approve the terms and conditions set forth in this policy. The use, collection and retention of client information is detailed herein.

The Bank’s systems and equipment are supervised and verified to ensure that they are optimally functioning and protect against inappropriate use. The verifications conducted may lead to the collection, recording, and analysis of data that is received, transmitted or stored by our systems about our clients, for example IP addresses. If there is reason to believe during the verification of the systems that illegal activity has taken place then it is possible that the information may be turned into the local authorities for further investigation.

## Consent

By using our website(s), you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

## Use of Information

Information contained in the europacbank.com website is subject to change at any given moment. Redistribution and copying of the information contained herein is prohibited without the previous written consent by Euro Pacific Bank. All information on the site is placed with care for accuracy but the bank is not responsible for updating or modifying the information contained herein. The use of third party or affiliate links on this website are accessed at your own risk and Euro Pacific Bank is not to be made liable for any and all information contained in the site, nor is the bank responsible for the privacy policy of those companies.

## Information Sharing

The Bank will not knowingly share personal information with third parties, except as permitted and accepted by law. A third-party affiliate or company are those companies and organizations that are not controlled by the Bank such as intermediate banks or prepaid card services provider. All information provided is under an agreement that it is strictly confidential and may only be used for the purpose of providing the service.

## Password Security and Safekeeping

Information concerning your account at Euro Pacific Bank must be accessed by the secure online banking system. The customer is fully responsible for the confidentiality of the information regarding your access to the online banking system, as well as any information pertaining to your account. The client also agrees that they will notify the bank of any unauthorized activity or security violation that takes place in the account. The use or access of a person’s account is prohibited unless the owner(s) of the account has given you consent to do so. Euro Pacific Bank will not be held liable or responsible for any losses that occur due negligence or incompliance of the obligations explained.

## Privacy

To view and download the privacy policy please access https://europacbank.com/legal/privacy-policy/. The Privacy Policy is part of the [Terms and Conditions](https://europacbank.com/legal/account-agreement-individual-corporate-accounts/) for proper and authorized use of our online banking site. Additionally, the use of this website confirms that you understand that not all internet connections are 100% safe, private or secure therefore, accepting these terms you understand that any information that is shared through this website may read by others.

## Protecting Your Information In Online Forms

Messages you send to us or we send to you through our secure messaging system is encrypted. If you send us messages through other sources, they might not be please use our secure messaging system.

## Spam

Euro Pacific Ban does not send unsolicited e-mails to you. Any emails sent are for the expressive use of communication that have been authorized through the bank contract and for the exclusive use of informing you news or relevant details regarding your account.

## Website Privacy Policy

At Euro Pacific Bank, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by www.europacbank.com and how we use it. If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at info@europacbank.com.

## Log Files

www.europacbank.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, www.europacbank.com uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons.

Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their website.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.europacbank.com, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that www.europacbank.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Third Party Privacy Policies

Euro Pacific Bank’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

## Children’s Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

This website does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in www.europacbank.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

Euro Pacific Bank reserves the right to at a very minimum, annually, make changes, modify or enhance the policy. The amended policy will be made available on our website so that you are made aware of any changes.

## Other Jurisdictions

Currently, there is no formal legislation regulating data protection in the British Virgin Islands (BVI) or Saint Vincent and the Grenadines.

The BVI Government has pledged that data protection legislation, based on international standards, may enacted in the near future. English Common law is persuasive (although not binding) in the BVI and accordingly, a BVI Court will recognize and subscribe to the Common law duties of confidentiality and privacy.

## Contacting Euro Pacific Bank

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, you may contact us at 1-888-527-4041 or at compliance@europacbank.com.
